Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Biology, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, pre-1991; Series 1
  - Uyeyama, Irene, Effect of experimental diabetes mellitus on protein synthetic activity of free and bound ribosomes of rat liver.., 1971-1972 (Box 12)
  - Van Le, Linda, The absence of immunosuppression in toxoplasma-infected mice.., March 1979 (Box 12)
  - Vavra, Jay Steven, An Ecological Study of Coastal Aboriginals in Northwestern Baja California.., 1987 (Box 12)
  - Vaysburd, Marina, 'Blocking' Peptide Immunotherapy in the Non-obese Diabetic Mouse.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Vereschagin, Kenneth S., The Effects of Exercise Training on Blood Volume in Cardiac Innervated and Denervated Patients.., May 1982 (Box 12)
  - Virgin, Charles, Jr., Glucocorticoids, Glia, and Glucose Uptake.., June 1989 (Box 16)
  - Wachtel, John S., The effects of chlorine on mammalian cells in tissue culture.., March 10, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Wait, William B., Jr., Investigation into the Circadian Control of Sleep State.., May 1982 (Box 12)
  - Waldvogel, Jerry A., A predator-prey study on the short-eared owl and the common meadow vole.., June 1976 (Box 12)
  - Wallstrom, James, The Effect of Cam in Corticosterone Levels of 12-, 16- and 20-Day-Old Rat Pups: A Study of the Ontogeny of Suppression.., 1983 (Box 12)
  - Walter, Louise C., Reduced Cell Spreading on Laminin is Associated With Altered Glycosylation of the Integrin Laminin Receptor in a Mutant Melanoma Cell Line.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Wang, Charles (Chao) Vin, Linkage Studies in Canine Narcolepsy.., June 1989 (Box 16)
  - Wang, Chia-Ying, The Measurement of Heat Shock Protein 70 Levels to Predict the Heat Response of Cells.., June 1989 (Box 16)
  - Wang, Christina H., The investigations of Tolerance induction in the Murine System Via Soluble HLA Class I Antigen.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Wang, Jeffrey Chun, Intervention in the Adult Respiratory Distress Syndrome: Blocking the Activation of Polymorphonuclear Granulocytes.., 1987 (Box 12)
  - Wang, Lena Tse-Ju, Gonococcal Pili Synthetic Peptide Analogues: receptor Blocking Function.., 1984 (Box 12)
  - Warner, Gayle L., An Examination of Ecology, Culture, and Morality in Selected Environmental Writers From 1945-1981.., May 1982 (Box 12)
  - Weddaburne, Claudia Marie, Sleep apnea as a cause of hypertension.., Spring 1977 (Box 12)
  - Weiser, Jeffrey Neal, The organ distribution of intracellular "CBG-like" receptors and the Biosynthesis of CBG in the rat liver.., March 1978 (Box 12)
  - Weiss, Lisa K., Synthesis of DNA Polymerase Alpha Through the Cell Cycle.., June 9, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Weiss, Stuart Bryan, Oviposition Behavior in Eupydryas Editha at Edgewood.., 1982 (Box 12)
  - Weller, Sandra, A Biochemical and Genetic Analysis of the Mg++Ca++ ATPase of E. Coli.., June 1974 (Box 12)
  - Weng, Andrew P., The Role of Polymorphic Residues on the I-A Molecule in MHC-Restricted Presentation of Myelin Basic Protein to T Cells.., June 1989 (Box 16)
  - Weng, Elaine, Localization of Epitopes on Duck Hepatitis B Virus Core Protein.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - West, Jeffrey Alan, Mechanisms of In Vitro Angiogenesis.., 1984 (Box 12)
  - Wexler, Gary, Heterotopic Heart transplantation in the Kidney Capsule as a Model for the Evaluation of New Forms of Immunosuppression.., 1988 (Box 12)
  - Whalen, Raymond Keith, The effects of caloric and oral linoleic acid monoglyceride supplementation in Cystic Fibrosis.., 1981 (Box 12)
  - Whiteside, Connie, A study of the Antibodies Produced in Rabbits Exposed to a Free Living Amoeba, Chaos chaos.., March 1974 (Box 12)
  - Whitham, Ruth and Ellison, David, The Effects of Thalamic Intralaminar Lesions on the Cat on the Eye movements of REM Sleep.., Spring 1974 (Box 12)
  - Whitten, Kenneth, A Population of the Valley Pocket Gopher (Thomomys Bottae) on a Serpentine Soil.., Spring 1970 (Box 12)
  - Widder, Don, Studies on glycogen metabolism and its control in isolated rat liver parenchymal cells.., 1975 (Box 12)
  - Wilder, Richard Barry, The Amino Acid Sequence Involved in the Adsorption of Bovine Serum Albumin on Silicone Rubber.., January 1984 (Box 12)
  - Wilder, Robert Theodore, DNA repair in different regions of chromatin in human cells., May 1977 (Box 12)
  - Wilkins, Yvonne Diane, Possible factors in the etiology of osteogenic sarcoma., March 1978 (Box 12)
  - Williams, David R., Evidence for Calcium as the Major Influx Ion in the Nerve Net of Sea Anemones.., March 1976 (Box 12)
  - Williamson, Brenda J., Hypertension and high blood pressure among blacks in the U.S.., 1973 (Box 12)
  - Wiser, Celeste Beryl, The American coot: a naturalistic study of behavior.., May 1978 (Box 12)
  - Witzer, Julie, Identification of the 5-Hydroxytryptamine1D Binding Sites in Human Frontal Cortex., 1998 (Box 12)
  - Wolden, Suzanne Leesa, Insulin Resistance induced by Obesity in the DW/DW Dwarf Rat.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Wolf, Rose Mary, Induction of humoral tolerance to platelet histocompatibility antigens.., April 1977 (Box 12)
  - Wong, Richard Jenshu, DHFR Gene Amplification in Ataxia Telangiectasia human Fibroblasts when Selected in Methotrexate.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Woolf, Alan, Schizophrenic vs. normal fibroblast metabolic profiles in a nutrient-loading test situation.., March 1972 (Box 12)
  - Wu, Anna P., Cardiac Allograft Prolongation in Rats Treated with Anti-CD4 Antibody and Post-transplantation Total-Lymphoid Irradiation Therapy.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Wu, Lena, Integration of Plasmid DNA Into Human Cells., June 9, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Wu, Thomas Dee, A Coupled Oscillator Model of the Multicaly-ceal Kidney.., 1983 (Box 12)
  - Yang, Eugene, Study of Presynaptic Facilitation in the Hippocampal Slice Preparation.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Yang, Phillip Chung-Ming, Differential Protective Effects of Varying Degrees of Hypoxia on the Cytotoxicities of Etoposide and Bleomycin.., 1984 (Box 12)
  - Yen, Janie, A Rapid in vitro Cytotoxicity Assay for the Detection of Tumor Necrosis Factor On Human BY-20 Cells.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Yen, Michael H., Cloning the cDNA of Rabbit CAP: An LPS-Neutralizing Protein.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Yu, Hee Keun, The Effect of Intron Mutations in Alternative RNA Splicing in Calcitonin/CGRP Gene.., June 1989 (Box 16)
  - Zanker, Darlene Ann, Effects of Foraging on Adrenocortical Activity and Behavior in Groups-Living Ovariectomized Squirrel Monkeys.., 1990 (Box 16)
  - Zeitlin, Pamela Leslie, Cholesterol exchange in vitro between microsomal and mitochondrial membranes isolated from rat liver.., March 1976 (Box 12)
  - Zirn, Jonathan Russell, The relationship of Glycomsaminoglycan composition to the hydrodynamic size of proteoglycan during rabbit articular cartilage maturation.., July 1982 (Box 12)
  - Zwieg, Gary, An Investigation of the Cytological Manifestations of Gene Amplification.., June 9, 1986 (Box 12)